我要一个总汇三明治--
I'll have the club sandwich--
-两片面包 薄片鳄梨 不要番茄 -好的
-two pieces of bread, avocado sliced thin, no tomato. -Check.
-你不用把这些写下来么? -没这个必要
-Uh, you're not gonna write any of this down? -I don't need to.
每个点单我都用快速记忆法来记忆
I remember every order with a handy mnemonics Device
利用首字母大写啊 蜘蛛侠电影什么的
Using state Capitals and Tobey Maguire movies.
你直接写下来不是更简单嘛
Or you could just write it down.
现在...记住了
And... it's locked in.
他才没记住 我们不能再坐兰迪负责的区域了
It is not locked in. We gotta stop sitting in Randy's section.
他总是把我们的菜单弄错
He always gets our order wrong
就因为他总不用笔记下来
because he never writes anything down.
如果你不是像个长岛来的姑娘一样点餐的话
You know, he'd probably get your food right
-说不定他就能给你拿对了 -干嘛呀你
-if you didn't order like a girl from long island. -Oh, mygod.
好了 别再抱怨了 我们都清楚
Okay, just please don't complain, 'cause we know
一旦被讨厌了 他们会对你的菜动什么手脚
what happens in the kitchen when they don't like a
你真的认为他们往你菜里吐了口水?
-customer. -Do you really think they spit in your food?
不，我觉得给我装宽带的那个人偷窥了我的裸体
No, I think my Cable guy has seen me naked.
我当然知道他们会往菜里吐口水 -我就不会 我可是
-I know they spit in our food. -Not me. I was
最优秀的服务生 重要的是销售策略
the best waitress. It's all about the up-sell.
就如 "先生
It's like, "oh, no,
您真的不需要再来一盘毛伊岛鸡肉吗?
you don't want another plate of maui wowie chicken bites?"
-现在还不想要吗 单亲爸爸们? -苍天啊
-How about now, table of divorced dads? -Damn.
又在讲你的毛伊岛鸡肉故事了?
You telling your maui wowie Chicken bites story?
我需要点新鲜故事了
-I need to get new stories.
喂 马科斯刚刚跟你讲话的那个人挺不错的
Hey, Max. That guy you were talking to was super cute.
-快给我透露点信息 -不清楚
-Give me dets. Come on. -I don't know. I
我没怎么注意 忙着为
wasn't paying attention. I was too busy making
通心粉和芝士的友好关系
up a song in my head about why Mac and cheese are best
-写首歌呢 - 嗨 马科斯很高兴认识你
-friends. - Hey, Max, it was great to meet you.
但我现在得走了 要不下次一起出去玩玩?
Look, I've gotta run, but do you want to go out sometime?
额 好啊 -太棒了 那星期五怎么样?
Uh, sure. -Great. All right. Well, how about Friday?
这是我的电话号码
That's my number.
很好 我再打给你 下次见 艾德里安
Okay. Great. I'll give you a call. Later, Adrian.
不错啊你!
Ooh! Yeah, girl!
黑人 英国的 还是同志?
Black, British, and gay?
行啊你 -是啊
Fabulous. - Yeah.
他一走进酒吧 那是伦敦大桥垮下来啊
That guy walks into a bar, it's London britches falling down.
伙计们 这是"欲望都市"第二季么?
Guys, what is this, "sex and the city," season two?
啦啦啦啦啦 我已经录下了
Oh! La, La, La, la, la! Have it on dvr.
你不会不打算给他打电话吧? 你脑残了吧
Wait a minute. You're not gonna call that guy? Are you nuts?
算了吧 他这么差劲 我看得出来
Come on. He sucks. I can tell.
马科斯你怎么总是这样?
Max, why do you always do this?
在了解一个人之前就放弃了?
Why do you always blow a guy off before you get to know them?
我才没有!
I don't do that!
这车太棒了 我一直想有一辆大功率车
This thing is sweet. I always wanted a muscle car.
对吧
Yeah, I know, right?
我最喜欢打开天窗
I love to just throw the top down
听着戴夫 马休斯乐队的劲爆摇滚
and blast Dave Matthews.
是啊
Yep.
这是滑坡效应 好吗?
It's a slippery slope, all right?
你现在不赶快放弃
You let one guy in that likes the Dave Matthews band,
接下来
the next thing you know,
就不可控制的走向
you're playing Frisbee Golf and taking it
-认真的感情了 -这是你的总汇苏打水
-really seriously. -Okay, here is your club soda
搭配一盘番茄 就跟你点的一样 -番茄?
-and tomatoes on the side, just like you ordered. -Tomatoes? (gags)
额 这... -伙计们
Ooh. Uh... okay. -Uh, guys,
我--番茄--额-我对番茄...
I--tomato--I just... (gagging) I've got tomato...
没事没事 他对番茄过敏
it's okay. He's got a thing with tomatoes.
-把番茄给我 -我不能呼...我...
-Give me the tomatoes. -I can't even... I mean...
他要吐了?他不吐我也吐了 这...
so he'll vomit? No, if he throws up, I will. It's...
我没事 我很好 看吧 马科斯
I'm good. I'm good. Guys... see... Max. Honey.
给我 我把它拿到...我
Let me just--I think I'll take it to my--I
-不要  - 马科斯 马科斯给我--算了
-don't want 'em. -Max. Max. Max, give m--All right.
幸福终点站
第一季  第08集
==深影字幕组==
你到底对艾德里安有什么意见?
What was your problem with Adrian?
他又性感又完美
That guy was incredibly Hot and perfect. (scoffs)
多大点事儿啊 就因为他有英国口音?
What's the big deal? He has a British accent?
我也可以有英国口音
I could have a British accent.
(牙买加口音)"我们约在皇宫酒店喝
(jamaican accent) "Meet me at the palace for high
-下午茶吧" -完全听不懂
-tea, mon." -Okay, I have no idea what that was.
话说回来 他能在五分钟内说了什么
Seriously, what could he have possibly said in Five minutes
-让你不想跟他约会? -他太可怕了
-that made you not want to go out with him? -(sighs) He was kinda terrible.
总是不停说芝加哥熊队的事
He kept going on and on about the bears.
你不是喜欢芝加哥熊队吗
You love the bears.
但他总喜欢说"我们"两个字
Yeah, but he was one of those "We" guys.
比如"我们"要加强防守
Like,"we need play Better defense."
"我们"要坚守阵型
"We need to stick our blocks."
就好像你不是队伍的一员一样
It's like, you're not on the team. (chuckles)
马科斯我以前就跟你一样
Oh, Max. I used to be just like you.
我也曾找尽所有借口去讨厌一个人
I used to look for any excuse not to like a guy,
-这样就可以在他拒绝我前先拒绝他 -那是
-so that I could reject him before he rejected me. -Was
是在你睡了他之前还是之后?
that before or after you slept with every guy you met?
哦! 啦啦啦啦 我不要听
Ooh! (singsongy) La, La, La, la, la!
讲完了再告诉我
Let me know when you're done.
布拉德是我唯一不会以貌取人的人
Brad was the only guy that I didn't prejudge instantly,
-幸好如此 -这才是我的宝贝
-and thank god. -Aw, that's my boo.
我可以理解那些过去
I'm okay with Sloppy 22nds.
当然 在看到他收藏的
I mean, sure, I could've bailed
那些宝拉 阿布杜 单曲
when I saw his collection of Paula Abdul cassingles,
或是看到他把睡衣塞进裤子里后
or when I learned that he tucks his pajama shirt in.
曾经想过要放弃 -好了 到此为止
Okay, let's wrap this up.
无所谓了 我已经把他号码扔了
It doesn't matter. I threw away his number.
看这里...
Oh. Well... (chuckles)
你留着这个是因为真心觉得我跟他有机会
Okay, did you keep this because you think we really have a shot,
还是你只是
or because you're
-有收藏强迫症? -额...8比2
-an obsessive-compulsive whack job? -Mm... 80/20.
我只是觉得你要给他一个机会
I just think you should give him a chance.
试着约约会
Go out on one date with him.
也许他没想象的那么糟
He may not be as bad as you think he is.
好吧 我会跟他约会
All right. Fine. I'll go on a date with him,
但如果他再次把睡衣塞进裤子里
but the second he tucks his pajamas in, I'm out of
-就不是我的问题了 -难道睡觉就不能打扮
-there. -I don't understand why a brother can't look nice
好看点吗? 又不犯法
when he goes to bed. Is that a crime?
哦 莎拉
Oh, Sara.
哦 "阿莱克斯"?
Ohh. "Alex"?
额...是戴夫
No, it's... it's Dave.
我当然知道
No, I know.
我懂了 你是想玩角色扮演吧
Oh! I get it. You wanna do some role-playing.
不是 你背上的纹身写着"阿莱克斯"呢
No, you have a tattoo on your back that says "Alex."
额 这是纹身写的是...
Oh, my "Alex" tattoo is for...
阿莱克斯 特雷贝克?
Alex Trebek?
我知道很烂 但总比上个借口好
I know, but it was better than my last excuse.
是阿莱克斯... 山大 汉密尔顿
Alex... ander Hamilton.
联邦党人文集是他写的吧?
He wrote most of the federalist papers?
-太烂了吧 -就是啊 联邦党人文集应该是
-That is so crazy. -I know. I thought most of the federalist Papers
詹姆斯 麦迪逊写的才对 我很屌吧 宝贝?
were written by James Madison. Impressive, right, boo?
不好意思 我没注意听
Oh, I'm sorry. I wasn't listening.
我在想象那个艾德里安没穿衣服的样子
I was picturing that Adrian guy naked.
我也是
So was I.
-嗨 -戴夫正在说他那个
-Hello. Hey, al. -You know, Dave was just telling us
"阿莱克斯"纹身严重妨碍了他寻欢作乐
about how his "Alex" tattoo is totally killing his game.
-是吗?大场面? -没什么凶猛的角色
-Oh. Is it? Big game? -No, not big game. Not bison.
就一两只温顺的小鹿 偶尔来只角马
Just the occasional deer or two. Maybe a gnu.
你呢?
How about you?
"戴夫"纹身带来什么困扰吗?
Is your "Dave" tattoo messing up your game?
-有一点 所以我才把它除掉了 -是吗?
-Oh. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, that's why I got it removed. -You did?
恩 我只是觉得是时候向前看了
Yeah, I just thought it was time to move on.
再加上不想一直重复我是戴夫 奥斯本的
Plus, I got tired of saying I was a super Dave Osborne
-超级粉丝 -什么?!怎么会有人不想承认
-fan. -What?! how could you get tired of telling people you're
是他的超级粉丝?
a super Dave Osborne fan?
也许我也该把它除掉了
-Well, maybe I should get mine removed, too.
-也许你该这么做 -我会的
-Maybe you should. -Well, maybe I will.
-也许你真的该这么做 -我真的会的
-(chuckles, mouth full) Maybe you should. -Maybe I will.
-很好 -我正试着清清除脑海里不停重复的
-okay. -I'm just trying to clear something up in my head
那句话 你是戴夫 奥斯本的超级粉丝吗?
as I go over it again.Are you a super Dave Osborne fan, or are
还是你只是不想再说你是他的超级粉丝?
you tired of telling people you're a super Dave Osborne Fan?
你这有意思吗?
Why do you do this?
-菜来了 请享用 -谢谢
-There we go. Enjoy. -Thank you.
他这次有任何一道菜上对了吗?
Is any of it right?
至少装在盘子里这件事是对的
It's on a plate.
-我的挺不错啊 -彭 别为他找理由了
-Well, mine looks fine. -Penn, stop defending him.
你明明跟他说你对坚果过敏
You told him you're allergic to nuts,
结果你的沙拉上全是核桃
and your salad's all pecan-crusted.
没关系 我可以吃旁边的这些...
It's okay.  I'm just gonna eat around it, so...
天啊 我不能呼吸了
Oh, my God.   My throat's closing.
-我受够了 喂! -别这样 别这样
-Okay. This has gotta stop. Hey! - No, no.
算了吧 当服务生真的不容易
Okay, look, please. It's really hard to be a waiter.
算... -彭
Just... -Penn,
他需要一些有建设性的批评意见
he needs to hear some constructive criticism.
我明白 但是...
I know, but...
这样可以提高工作表现
it'll make him better at his job.
-他以后会感谢我的 服务员! -有事吗?
-He'll thank me for it in the long run. Dude! -What's up?
兰迪 你以后得把菜单写下来了
Randy, you gotta start writing stuff down, man.
-我没点派 彭妮差点呛死 -你说反了吧
-I didn't order pie. Penny almost died. -Feel like you should be flipping those.
就是 他也总是把我点的弄错
Yeah, he always gets my order Wrong, too.
兰迪 又有人投诉你吗?
-Randy, are you getting more complaints?
不是 只是我正在用的这种记忆法--
No, it's just, I have this mnemonic device that I'm using--
我不是说过不能再被投诉了吗?
I told you this can't happen again, all right?
-出门左拐，因为你被解雇了 -什么?
-Hit the road. You're fired. -What?
我说你被解雇了!
You're fired!
真是多谢你们了 所有这些...我都记住了
Oh, thanks a lot, man! Oh, and this... it's locked in.
但我...是你说...
But I... you said...
现在谁都不认识我了?
Oh, so now y'all don't know nobody?
真的假的?你们就这样对我?
For real? That's what's hot in the streets?
你纹这个的时候什么情况?
So how hammered were you when you got this thing?
简单来说，一大把的头发都被我扯下来了
Let's just say there was a lot of hair-holding.
-我要吐了 我又要吐了 -没事的 天啊
-Hold my hair. Hold my hair. -Okay. I got it. Oh, jeez.
加油!狗熊队
Go, bears!
加油!
加油!狗熊队！哥呀
Go, bears! Whoa!
听起来挺悲催的
Sounds like a lot of fun.
咱们把这贱人名字弄掉吧
What do you say we blast this bitch's name off, huh?
不是啦 你误会了
Oh. Whoa. No, no. It's--it's not like that.
- 我们还是好朋友 -哦 又是这种
- We're actually still friends. - Oh. One of those.
-看样子你还余情未了啊 -不是的 只是-
-Sounds like you have some unresolved feelings going on. -No, no. It's just that--
-啥时分的手啊? -四个月前吧
-when did you break up? -About four months ago.
-四个月前 恩 -不好意思
-Four months ago. Uh-huh. -I'm sorry.
你干嘛把这些写下来? 跟这又没什么关--
Why are you writing that down? This has nothing to do with--
以我的经验来看 如果一段感情真的结束了
in my experience, if someone is truly over someone else,
就会马上把纹身去掉
they get those taken off right away.
恩 你知道的 我真的很忙
Well, I've been really busy, you know,
买V领T恤 穿V领T恤
buying V-neck T-shirts, wearing V-neck T-shirts.
这个真的占了我很多时间
It pretty much usurped most of my time.
是啊 你要搞清楚两件事
Exactly. There are two things you need to understand.
第一 我不在乎你说的是真是假
One, I do not validate,
第二 在你消掉纹身之前
and two, you shouldn't get this done
你应该把你窝着的感情先消掉
until you have all your feelings worked out.
要知道 消纹身是永久性的
You really need to understand, tattoo removal is permanent.
一旦你把纹身去掉 就不能再纹上去了
Once you have a tattoo taken off, you cannot put it back on.
是吗，不是可以再重新--
Really? 'cause I feel like I could just--
嗯 嘘 嘘 好好想想我说的话
uh, shh, shh, shh. Just... think about what I said, okay?
你不介意的话
Now if you'll excuse me,
我现在要帮一个女人去掉她脸上的五角星纹身
I have to go remove a face pentagram
她参加了市政会竞选 我还投了她一票
from a woman who's running for city council. She's got my vote.
哇 三倍分区的二十分 我又赢了 克莱德
Boom! Triple 20! I win again, Clyde!
我才不管你记不记得你投到哪里了
I don't care that you don't remember where you are.
噢 噢 别走 听到了吧?
Oh. Oh. Don't go anywhere, okay?
哈啰?
Hello?
嗨 是我 简
Hey, it's Jane.
你跟那个英国小帅哥的约会怎么样了?
How's your date going with the brit boy?
噢 酷毙了 我知道艾德里安
Oh, it's awesome. I know, Adrian.
切尔西 韩德勒 演得很假
Chelsea Handler has forgotten how to keep it real.
我们真的很来电
We're really hitting it off.
噢 太好了 嗯
Oh, I'm so glad to hear that. Mm-hmm.
真的太棒了 -噢噢噢艾德里安刚走
That is just fantastic. -Ooh-Hoo-Hoo-hoo! Hey, you just missed Adrian.
你怎么没在约会?
Why aren't you on your date?
嗯... 我不是很想去
Uh... look, I wasn't into it.
而且 我还要跟克莱德叙叙旧
Besides, I needed to reconnect with Clyde.
你是打电话取消约会了 还是放他鸽子了?
So did you at least call to cancel, or did you stand him up?
你放他鸽子了?
You stood him up?
噢 这没什么大不了的
Oh. It's not a big deal.
那你说他打电话问你在哪里
-Well, what did you say
你怎么说的?  -他根本没打电话
when he called to find out where you were? -He didn't call.
那你怎么知道他没有放你鸽子?
Well, then how do you know he didn't stand you up?
什么? 你真心疯了
what? You're out of your mind.
我是说 是不是你的魅力用完了 嗯?
I mean, is it possible that Max got maxed, huh?
好吧 第一 我很喜欢你把我的名字用作动词
Okay, one, I love how you used my name as a verb.
要成为文化偶像的第一要素
Big part of becoming a cultural icon,
你知道这是我的目标
which you know is a goal of mine.
第二 闭上你的鸟嘴
Two, you shut your whore mouth!
噢 踩到你痛处了?
Ooh. Touched a nerve?
没人比我更有魅力
No one maxes Max.
现在 拿上你的外套
Now Let's go grab whatever wasp overcoat you wear.
我们去那家酒吧看看
We're gonna go down to that bar
那个瘦得像皮包骨的英国笨蛋
and see that he's sitting there
肯定还坐在那里 说着
like a skinny, British Loser, all like...
(伦敦腔)"马科斯在哪里?
(British accent) "Where's Max?
他没来 我的心都碎了" -你的衬衣穿反了
He broke my heart by Not showing up." -Your shirt inside out?
对 我的衬衣是穿反了
yep. My shirt is inside out.
-嗨 -嗨 我有点事情想问你
-Hey. -Hey. I just wanted to ask you something.
好 进来吧 我正在泡茶
Yeah. Come on in. I was just making myself some tea.
-你要喝点吗? -不 不用了
-Do you want some? -No, I'm good.
嗯 我问你
Um, let me ask you somethin'.
我们分手了多久 你才把纹身去掉的?
How soon after the whole thing did you get your tattoo removed?
哦 我的纹身 问得好
Oh, my tattoo. Excellent question.
嗯 我不记得了 大概一个星期吧
Um, I don't know, like, a week or so. Oh.
是吗 这么快
Yeah. That was fast.
是啊 你的纹身也去掉了吗?
Yeah. Did you get yours taken off?
又是个自由的花花公子了?
You free to be a playa?
-不要说"花花公子" -我一说完就后悔了
-Don't say "playa." -I regretted it almost immediately.
-有留疤吗? -嗯 有一点
-So was there any scarring? -Yeah. A little. Yeah.
你愿意让我看一下吗 看看会是什么样子
Do you mind if I took a look, just to see what I'm in for?
-不 我不愿意 -我不是说让你脱光什么的
-Nah. I don't think so. -I-I wasn't trying to get you naked or anything.
哦 我知道 我知道你不是那个意思
No, I know. I know that's not what you
-是啊 反正我们已经脱过几百次了
meant. -Yeah, 'cause it-- it wouldn't be weird,
也不会觉得很奇怪  -是啊
because we've done it, like, a million times. -Yeah,
大概脱了几百几千次了 是吧?
like, a million bajillion times, right?
但我不知道该不该脱
Yeah. But I don't know.
-现在脱是很奇怪  -不 不奇怪
-Now it's weird. -No, it's not.
不 奇怪 -不奇怪
No, it is.  -It's not weird.
很奇怪 -是有点奇怪
Yeah. Ah, it's weird. -It's a little weird.
嗯 你会收到我发的
Look, um, you're about to get
一条特别长的道歉短信 别看了
a really long apologize-y text from me. Don't read it.
我是不得不发
I just have to send it.
我跟你说艾德里安没有放我鸽子
I'm telling you, Adrian did not stand me up.
我就是个稍微胖点的克里斯 奥唐纳
I'm like a chubby Chris O'Donnell,
在芝加哥 我就是真正的克里斯 奥唐纳
which in Chicago is like a regular Chris O'Donnell.
好了 冷静点 哇 马科斯
All right. Calm down. Wow, Max.
他们在艾德里安给你挑的桌子上做鳄梨沙拉酱
Adrian picked a place where they make guacamole at your table.
你不是说等你有钱了
Didn't you say that when you come into some money,
你就要跟那样的女人
you were gonna get one of those ladies to come live
给你现场做饭?  -我没说过
at your house?  -I don't think that I said that.
再说 她酸橙用太多了
Besides, she's using a lot of lime.
我没看到艾德里安哦
I don't see Adrian anywhere.
嗯 他可能在卫生间
Yeah. He's probably in the bathroom writing
给我写情歌
Elliott Smith-type Songs about me.
请问 你有没有看到一个
Excuse me. You seen a guy named
叫艾德里安的英国黑小伙?
Adrian--black, British?
哦 有 我认识他  之前我们是室友
Oh, yeah. I know him. We used to be roommates.
起码在他到狗熊队做前台接待之前
Well, at least until he got that front office job with the bears.
这就是为什么他说"我们" 他说的是他们!
That's why he was saying "we." He's them!
而且他在狗熊队上班 太酷了
He works for the bears. That is pretty cool.
简 这里是芝加哥
Jane, it's chicago.
人人都在为狗熊工作
Everybody works for the bears.
那艾德里安今晚在哪儿? -他没来这
So where's Adrian tonight? -He didn't come in tonight.
他没来? -星期五的晚上
He didn't? -On Fridays
他通常会去阿瓦隆剧院
he usually goes to the Avalon theater
过一个很棒的"烂片之夜"  一堆人坐一起
for good bad movie night. A bunch of people sit around
看一部烂片再一起嘲笑电影 很讽刺吧
and watch a bad movie and make fun of it. It's ironic.
加柠檬片吗?  -嗯 我的不用加
Orange whips? -Uh, no orange whips for me.
告诉姐这个人不适合你
Tell me this guy doesn't sound perfect for you.
所以我说你应该给别人机会
This is why you have to give people a chance.
他本来可以成为你的BRAD!
He could be your Brad!
只是他的伦敦腔，而且更酷
Except for British and way cooler.
你觉得我的婚姻有问题吗?
Do you think my marriage is in trouble?
走吧 我们去阿瓦隆剧院
Come on. We're going to the Avalon.
你会跟他道歉 然后真的跟他约会?
What, so you can apologize and ask him out on a real date?
不是 是因为我发火了
No! 'cause I'm pissed!
我真的很抱歉我害兰迪被炒了
I feel bad for getting Randy fired.
我想补偿他  -都这样了
I wanna make it up to him. -At this point, I
我觉得你最好别管了
really just think you should leave it alone.
不不不 我有个很棒的法子
No, no, no. I know the perfect thing.
-这个不行 -噢
-No. -Mnh.
-这个就好多了 -嗯
-This is much better. -Mm-hmm.
嗨
Hey!
你们在这干什么?你们在跟踪我吗?
What are you guys doing here? Are you stalking me?
伙计 我很抱歉 所以我带了礼物过来
Look, man, uh, I feel bad, so I bought this gift basket
希望你原谅我害你被炒
to apologize for getting you fired.
等一下 你被炒了?
Wait. You got fired?
肯定是因为没有做笔记
I bet it was for not writing stuff down.
不不不 是因为 不 宝贝
-No, no. No, it's--no, b--
是因为我摸别人屁股
It's because I touched someone's butt.
--他为什么被炒? -嗯 他摸我屁股?
-Why did he get fired? -Uh, he touched my butt?
我受够了! 你总是不愿意做笔记
I'm tired of you not writing stuff down!
电话留言你不记，我们的纪念日
You forgot phone messages, our anniversary,
还有我爸妈来城里你都不记下来
when my birth parents came to town!
拿笔写一下有那么难吗?! -说点什么啊
How hard is it to grab a pencil?! -Say something.
伙计 她说得对 写下来也只要几秒钟
Dude, she's right. Writing stuff down only takes, like, a second.
不是让你说这个
No, not that.
兰迪 我们结束了 免得你忘了 写下来!
We're done, Randy, and in case you forget, write it down.
宝贝--
Okay, B--
-嗯..嗯.. -她只是要点时间冷静一下
-mm. Mm, mm, mm. -I think she just needs a second to calm down.
是啊
Yeah.
顺便告诉你 你的乐队逊毙了
And by the way, your band sucks.
我都不知道你哪个更差劲，弹吉他还是做爱!
I don't know what you're worse at, guitar or sex!
不!
No!
有点伤人吧
Stings a bit.
马科斯你有什么计划?
Max, what exactly is your plan here?
你打算冲过去跟他吵一架吗?
You're just gonna run in There and start yelling?
我没什么计划 不过你的计划不错
I don't have a plan, but I like your plan.
我没钱!帮我买票!
I don't have any money! Pay for my ticket!
嗨 两张杰西 斯帕诺的波波
Hi. Two, please, for Jessie Spano's boobs.
艾德里安?艾德里安? 嗯?
Adrian? Adrian? Huh?
艾德里安?艾德里安? -马科斯?
Adrian? Adrian? -Max?
-艾德里安, 嗨! -你在这干什么?
-Adrian, hey! -What are you doing here?
-嘘 -你闭嘴 老兄
-Shh! - You shush, bro.
我有私事要说
I'm trying to have a personal conversation
-我还要看电影呢 老兄
here. -I'm trying to watch the movie here,bro.
老兄 你想跟我干一架吗?
Bro, you do not want to get into a bro-off with me, bro.
砰!鄙视你!
Boom! Shamed!
你想怎么样?
What do you want?
我来是要告诉你 虽然你的工作不错
I came to let you know that even though you have an awesome job,
虽然你是个英国黑小伙，也就是说你很性感
and you're black and British, which is super sexy,
虽然你知道哪里能做鳄梨沙拉酱
and you know a place to make magic happen out of an avocado
但是你不能...噢 天啦
and a pestle, doesn't give you the right to--Oh, my god.
这是"我是舞蹈演员
Is this the "I'm a dancer,
不是脱衣舞女"的场景吗?
not a stripper" scene?
帅呆了 (西班牙语)
Awesome. Yo soy bailarina. Yo No soy Unastripper.
-还是西班牙语的?酷毙了 -嗯
-In Spanish? Amazing. -Ahem.
-但是你不能放我鸽子 -我没有放你鸽子
-You can't stand people up. -I didn't stand you up.
嘘!是吗?
Shh! Yeah?
那为什么酒保说你没来?
Then how come the bartender said you weren't there?
我在酒吧外面...
I was waiting outside...
-哦 你在外面 -像个绅士一样
-Oh, you were outside? -Like a gentleman.
那很好 非常绅士
That's actually very nice. It's super polite.
嗯 我就是这样的人 这
-Mm. That's the kind of guy I am. It's... it's
没什么  -嗯 我觉得我们有个很好的开始
nothing. -Look, I feel like we got off to a rocky start.
我说点什么 你也说点什么
I said some things. You said some things.
实际上 我什么也没说
-Actually, I didn't say anything.
我的意思是我很高兴
My point is that I'm actually glad it worked out
一切都进展得很顺利 我找你的时候
the way it did. I mean, I learned a ton about you
知道了很多你的事  -噢 那很好 马科斯
while I was trying to track you down. -Oh, that's nice, Max.
你知道你怎么能更了解我吗? -微博?
Do you know how else you could have learned about me? -Facebook?
不 我们有约的时候你应该来
No. By Turning up for our date.
抱歉 马科斯我不和乱放鸽子的人约会
Sorry, Max. I don't date guys who play games.
看看是谁被惹毛了 兄弟
Look who got served now, bro.
闭上你的臭嘴 好吗? 他刚被伤了心
You shut your whore mouth, okay? He just got his heart broken.
是啊 我尴尬之极 但你也没好到那里去!
Yeah, this was embarrassing, but this is embarrassing, too!
你居然一个人看电影! 寂寞吧!
You're on a date with no one! You're alone!
好吧 享受电影吧
Okay. Enjoy the movie.
是啊 好好看电影
Yeah, enjoy the movie.
享受独自约会 嗯?  - 停
Enjoy your date, huh?  - No,
我们不用再  我们不用再打扰他了
we don't need any--no. We don't need any more words.
是啊 好吧 你和空气两个人 嗯?
No more--all right. Yep. You two come together-- you and no one, huh?
好了 那里没人 我们都知道他一个人在那
Okay. There's no one there. We all know there's no one there.
你注定要孤独终老了!
You'll be alone for the rest of your life!
送你个称号! 傻蛋大胡子!
Know how I can tell? That stupid beard!
# 我在打扫 我在打扫 #
I'm dusting, I'm dusting
# 我从贾斯汀那购物归来 #
I bought this from a guy named Justin
#贾斯汀长得英俊潇洒 如我兄弟一般 #
Justin's supercute, and he looks like my cousin
# 这首歌立马变了味 #
This song got really super strange fast
纯鼓声演奏
drum solo!
# 嗨哈 #
Hi-hat
今天是我们的周年纪念日
so it's our anniversary,
我知道你总想去一趟巴黎
and I know that you've always wanted to go to Paris,
- 因此我买了两张头等舱的票  -什么?
- so I priced out two first-class tickets...  - what?
但我意识到自己只是个服务生而且要还
And then I realized I'm a waiter with $40,000
四万元的学生贷款 不过我还是买了这个
in Student Loan debt, and I got you this instead.
哦
Oh.
这个  这个事实上要比
That's... that's way better
真的去趟巴黎要有意义得多 对吧?
than an actual trip to Paris, right?
- 卢浮宫不算什么   - 转过来看看
- Louvre, shmoove.  -  Turn it over.
你愿意搬来和我一起住吗?
Would you wanna move in with me?
哦 我的天 当然愿意!
Oh, my god. Yes! Yes?
愿意  - 愿意
Yes.  - Yes.
愿意 天哪 不过我们得把厕所的门关掉
- Yes. Awesome, except We gotta keep the bathroom door shut.
那些夫妇总会吓到我
Those couples just creep me out.
那么
So...
你想去掉什么纹身?
what are you having removed?
我背上的一头巨鹰
On my back I got this giant eagle
它站在骷髅上与野牛搏斗
fighting a bison on top of a skull made out of lava,
边上有五头豹子蓄势待发
while five panthers wait
要撕裂残渣败类的尸骨
to rip apart the carcass of the loser.
你呢?
You?
额  也是一只鹰
Uh... it's a Hawk...
从头盖骨处啃食林肯总统的脑子
eating Abe Lincoln's brains out of his top hat,
周围是
wrapped in a...
嘿 阿莱! 你来这里干嘛?
Hey, Al! What are you doing here?
正点
Sweet.
阿莱 你留着那个纹身 为什么要骗我?
Al, you've still got the tattoo. Why'd you lie?
过来说话 我也不明白
Come here. I don't know.
这简直 我无法忍受你这么轻易就
You know, it just--it really hurt to think it was so easy
要去掉纹身 我的意思是 即便几个月过去了
for you to get rid of it. I mean, it's been months,
- 我还是狠不下心  - 那么好吧
- and I still can't bring myself to do it.  - Okay, well,
说老实话 其实我也并非因为
if we're gonna be completely honest, I didn't bail
会留下疤痕才没去掉纹身
on getting mine off just because of the scars and stuff.
是时候了 对吗?
But it's time, right?
好吧 那我们就一起做吧
Yeah. So then Let's do it together.
看着 面对激光的疼痛
Look, if we are gonna face lasers,
我们需要壮一下胆 狗尾酒?
we're gonna need some help. A little tail of the dog?
是狗毛酒（解醉酒）
It's hair of the dog.
- 随便了 反正我只喜欢猫  - 我也是
- What do I care? I'm a cat person.  - I'm a cat person, too.
哟
Whew.
哦 记得我们上次喝这玩意的时候吗?
Ah. Ohh. Do you remember the last time we drank that stuff?
只记得第二天早上了
I only remember the morning after.
哦
Ooh.
啊
Aah.
哦 头好痛
Oh, my head.
哦 天哪 我记得的最后一件事是
Oh, god. The last thing I remember...
哦 和你一个劲的拼酒
ohh. Is doing body shots off your stomach.
不是我 是那酒保
That was not me. That was the bartender.
他是个好人 嗯
He was a nice man. Mm-hmm.
嗯 嗯 嗯
Mm. Mm. Mm.
嗯
Hmm.
Mm.
我的肩膀怎么那么酸?
Why is my shoulder so sore?
嗯?
Hmm?
哦 大概是这个的缘故吧
Oh. Maybe it has something to do with that.
啊! 我纹了身!
Aah! I got a tattoo!
哦
ohh.
这样做好贴心啊
I think it's kinda sweet, you know? Ohh.
就像是
It's kinda like...
即使不在你身边 也从未远离 对吧?
even when I'm not with you, I still will be, you know?
噢
Ow.
喔 天哪 不!
Oh, hell, no!
哦! 你胯上纹了个"戴夫"
Oh! You got a "Dave" tattoo on your hip!
- 该死!  - 我的名字留在你身上了!
- No!  - My name on your beautiful body!
- 哦!感觉像是流氓一样  - 你才不是
- Ohh! I look like an extra on "Oz."  - You really don't.
我们算是互相纹身的情侣档吗?
Are we really that couple that has matching tattoos?
我认为这很可爱 不是吗?
I think it's-- it's cute, you know?
这是个美好的故事 以后讲给孩子听
It'll be, uh, a great story we can tell our children.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
无与伦比的一个早晨
That was a fun morning.
是啊
Easy.
哦!哦! 你觉得这是个错了吗?
Whew. Ooh.  Do you think we made a mistake?
是啊 是啊 弥天大错
Yeah. Yeah, we made a huge mistake.
哦
Ohh.
噢! 噢! 噢! 啊!啊!啊! 好痛!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Ow! Ow! Ow, that hurts!
哎哟! 好痛啊! 好痛啊!
Ow! That hurts! That hurts!
兰迪的前任说他们分手后就再没见过
So Randy's ex says she hasn't seen him since they broke up.
你知道吗?他可能过得不错
You know what? He's probably fine.
或住在车里
Or living in his car.
是啊 或者鞋里
Yeah, or a shoe...
- 或在农场里喂独角兽  - 或者车里
- or a ranch, breeding baby unicorns.  - Or his car.
不 说正经的 他睡在车里呢
No, seriously. He's living in his car.
哦
Ohh.
嘿 伙计
Hey, fella.
嗨 你在里面做什么呢?
Hi. Whatcha doin' in there?
首先你害我被炒鱿鱼 然后你让我无家可归
First you get me fired. Then you get me kicked out of my house.
现在我还不能睡在自己的车里 嗨 你好吗?
Now I can't even sleep in my own car. Hi. How are you?
- 嗨  - 那么一切都好吗?
- Hi.  - So things are good?
哦 不能再好了 没有家 没有女朋友
Oh, great. Uh, no house, no girlfriend.
乐队也开除我了 我之所以能加入因为
My band just kicked me out, which they only let me join
我让他们在餐馆里白吃白喝
'cause I gave 'em free food from the restaurant.
听上去有人要单飞啦
Sounds like someone's going...solo.
听着 兄弟
Look, man.
我对发生的事情很抱歉
I'm really sorry about what happened.
我告诉你吧 你可以来我办公室工作
I'll tell you what. I'm gonna get you a job at my office.
不 是认真的吗?
No. Are--seriously?
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.
我 看起来 是吗? 因为这个
- That--I--see--really? 'cause that would--
这个棒极了 伙计 谢谢你
that would be awesome, man. Thank you.
哦 是啊 乐意效劳
- Oh, yeah. Happy to do it.
嗯 周一打我电话 嗯 我的号码是
Uh, call me on Monday. Uh, take my number down.
是的 好啊
- Yes.Okay. Yeah.
- 312487  - 312487
- It's 312-487...  -  312-487...
- 你在做什么?  - 我在记忆
- what are you doing?  -  I'm locking it in.
我的大脑如电脑一般 正在输入当中
I got a brain like a computer, so just hit me with it.
是啊 我告诉过你的 这是个助记术
Yeah. Like I told you, it's just a mnemonic device, which is
用来增强记忆 可以用在任何事上
simply a memory aid. I mean, you can use 'em really for anything.
有用来记五大湖的 还有记忆轨道行星的
I have one for the great lakes, one for the planets that
嗯 另外还有美国总统山的头像的
are in Orbit, uh, the-- the heads of Mount Rushmore.
比一般的记忆方法要稍许复杂些
It is--it's a little more complex than the others.
你没有去掉纹身?
So you didn't get them removed?
没 过去它们是我们爱情的见证
No. No, those tattoos were a symbol of our bond as a couple,
现在变成了友情的化身
and now they're a symbol of our bond as friends.
是啊 你们知道 对于那些
Yeah, you know, you can't
有特殊意义的事总是难以割舍
just get rid of something that special just like that.
激光太疼了?
- Hurt too much?
疼的要人命!
Like a bitch! Yeah.
不得不说 马科斯你居然打我电话了
I gotta say, Max, I'm really surprised you called.
嘿 别担心
Hey, don't worry.
- 我不再迷戴夫 马休斯了  - 很好啊
- I'm not into Dave Matthews anymore.  - It's all good.
我不再是那个凭一件事就判断别人的人了
I'm not the type of guy to judge someone over one thing anymore.
最近好吗?
So how's everything going?
哦 还不错 嗯 经常出去兜风
Oh, it's good, man. Uh, just hanging out.
- 嗯  - 我卖了那辆破旧老爷车
- Mm-hmm.  - I finally traded in that old muscle car,
换成2001款克莱斯勒越野车
and now I'm rocking a cherry 2001 P.T. Cruiser.
- 好吧  - 然后 现在我极度专注于
- Okay.  - Yeah, oh, and I'm super excited
我为保罗 沃克开办的粉丝博客
about this fan blog I started for Paul Walker.
- 哦 真不错  - 嘿嘿 是的
- Oh, he's a guy.  -  Yeah.
我的意思是
I mean,
这些又让我们相逢了  - 的确
that pretty much catches us up to today.  - Good.
是啊 今天值得庆祝一番
Yeah, which is a great day,
因为我买了跟辫制的皮带
'cause I just got this braided belt.
好吧 我试过了 没办法
Okay, I gave it a shot. I'm done.
- 有进步嘛  - 是啊
- Baby steps.  - True.
好吧 我想来个母狼
Okay, so I want a she-wolf
和一头金属豹做爱 上面是燃烧的条形码
making love to a metal panther on top of a flaming bar code,
条形码下面 写上
and under that, I want it to say,
"我们地狱见 珍妮特"
"If there's a hell, I'll see you there, Janet."
你不写下来吗?
You gonna write that down?
不 都在我脑子里了
Nope. It's locked in.